#平時在家裡 我 就我一個人在家裡 我都隨便吃的
When I'm at home, I, when I'm alone at home, my meals are usually very simple,
#要麼榨菜
sometimes pickled mustard,
#要麼那個豆 豆豉 (註︰這個不太想音譯，但亦不想名字太Sophisticated，感覺好像很講究似的，所情願意思不太明白就算了)
or, you know, black, black beans.
#要麼那個
or, I mean,
#要麼那個 乾魚
or, I mean, dried fish.
#這很方便 很快捷的
It's really fast and convenient.
#搞碗飯 就可以吃了
Together with a bowl of rice, it's already a meal.
#一頓就這樣過去了
It's just a meal after all.
#等一下我還要煎兩個蛋來 剛好兄弟來了
I'll need to fry two eggs as well. My buddy has just arrived.
#這 太寒酸啦 這個
It's ah, too stingy, you know.
#先放點油
Put some oil first.
#油要稍微放多一點
I need slightly more oil.
#再搞點這個腐竹來炸一下 (註︰我不想在他的煎或炸著墨了，太多Pan fry, deep fry不好看，隨隨便便就算)
I fetch some, bean curd sheets too.
#加點鹽
Put some salt.
#好啦 這些菜都煮好啦
Alright! All dishes are ready.
#你看 這個火燒了一下 應該沒事
Look! This is slightly burnt. But It should be fine.
#搞一點試一下
Let me have a try.
#嗯 很香哦
Um! It smells good!
#這個雞蛋
The eggs,
#煎的
are fried.
#還有這個榨菜
And the pickled mustard too.
#剛好
Perfect!
#嗯 兄弟不知道跑哪裡去了
Um? My buddy is not around, where is he?
#等下我叫過他來一起吃飯啦
I'll call him back to have our meal together.
#好啦 今天的視頻就到這裡啦
Alright! The video ends here.